apfco.com 2018-12-21

# Arrowhead Promotion | Privacy | ArrowheadPromotion.com

Arrowhead Promotion & Fulfillment Co. Inc. (Arrowhead) is a provider of Sweepstakes, Rebates, Premiums, Sampling, Loyalty Programs and other Promotion-related Fulfillment Management Services as well as Customer Support Services. We manage and execute these promotions and programs on behalf of our clients' businesses. Many of these programs include the gathering of personally identifiable information as a requirement of consumer or business participation. 

This privacy policy tells you how we use the personal information collected. This includes the gathering of data at this site as well as the sites we build on our client's behalf, data gathered through mobile technology and through offline resources. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By providing your information through this site or other program sites, mobile entry or offline, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used. 

Collection and Use of Information  
We collect personally identifiable information, such as names, postal addresses, email addresses, etc., when voluntarily submitted by program participants or site visitors. Use of this data may include: consumer or business response, notification of potential winner, fulfillment of premiums or prizes, opt-in for future marketing efforts, program reporting, etc. This information is only used to fulfill these requirements above, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add your information to a mailing list. Personal identifiable information collected by Arrowhead on behalf of a client is the property of Arrowhead or our client. Arrowhead does not share this information with any 3rd party. Arrowhead is not responsible for data collected on behalf of clients when such data is in a client's possession. 

Cookie/Tracking Technology  
Our websites may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology; however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties. 

Distribution of Information  
We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes. 

Dispute Resolution  
Within the scope of this privacy notice, if a privacy complaint or dispute cannot be resolved through Arrowhead Promotion and Fulfillment Co., Inc.'s internal processes, Arrowhead Promotion and Fulfillment Co., Inc. has agreed to participate in the VeraSafe Privacy Shield Dispute Resolution Procedure. Subject to the terms of the VeraSafe Privacy Shield Dispute Resolution Procedure, VeraSafe will provide appropriate recourse free of charge to you. To file a complaint with VeraSafe under the Privacy Shield Dispute Resolution Procedure, please submit the required information to VeraSafe here: <https://www.verasafe.com/privacy-services/dispute-resolution/submit-dispute/>

Arrowhead complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union to the United States. Arrowhead has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, Arrowhead commits to resolve complaints about our collection or use of your personal information. EU individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding our Privacy Shield policy should first contact Arrowhead at: [inquiry@apfco.com](mailto:inquiry@apfco.com). 

Note: the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for Arrowhead managed programs and websites. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites. 

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, Arrowhead commits to the right of individuals to access their personal data. Our organization is subject to the investigatory and enforcement powers of the Federal Trade Commission (FTC) . In cases of onward transfer to third parties of data of EU individuals received pursuant to Privacy Shield, Arrowhead is potentially liable. 

Arrowhead recognizes the possibility, under certain conditions, for the individual to invoke binding arbitration and under certain conditions, more fully described on the Privacy Shield website at <https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=How-to-Submit-a-Complaint>, you may be entitled to invoke binding arbitration when other dispute resolution procedures have been exhausted. 

Privacy Contact Information  
If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below: 

By e-mail: [inquiry@apfco.com](mailto:inquiry@apfco.com)  
By Phone: (218) 327-1165 

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy at any time. 

_Google Analytics and Google Tag Manager GTM_  
This website uses Google Analytics, a web analysis service of Google. Google Analytics employs cookies that are stored to your computer in order to help analyze how visitors use this site. The anonymous information generated by these cookies, such as time, place and frequency of your visits to our site, including your IP address, is transmitted to Google. This web site has also implemented Google Analytics Adverting Features including demographics and interest reporting, remarketing, GDN impression reporting and Campaign Manager where Google Analytics collects additional data about this sites traffic. Google Tag Manager (GTM") is a tag management system to used for tracking and analytics on websites. Tags are small code elements that, among other things, are used to measure traffic and visitor behavior: to understand the effect of online advertising and social channels; to set up remarketing and orientation towards target groups; and to test and optimize websites. In addition, web site also uses Google AdWords Remarketing Service to advertise on third party websites including Google. 

How Google Uses Information from sites or apps that use Google Services:  
<https://policies.google.com/technologies/partner-sites>

More information about Googles privacy practices  
<https://www.google.com/analytics/tag-manager/use-policy/>

How to Opt out of Google Analytics:  
To prevent data from being used by Google Analytics, Google has developed the following opt-out add on.   
<https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/>  
Users can also optout of Google of cookies use by visiting Google Ad Settings  
<https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated>

Your California Privacy Rights  
California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits customer who are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please write to us at the following email address:
